briefly introduce about yourself and
your organization sure um Ian so I'm the
head of uh AI lab credential yeah um
what are you looking for at Vietnam
ftech Summit right so I think as a
presedential AI lab is just launched we
launched last week at 19th of November
uh we really are looking to build an
ecosystem with uh not just our research
centers our government but also startups
so we are looking for a new Innovative
you know next Generation AI that we can
deploy to our organization right so how
your experience with the event so far uh
yeah it's been great um did a short
sharing and then we had a panel session
I think some of them have been very
useful uh and I think really just
connecting with people and the people
that are here I think it's it's been
great thank you so much that's all for
today